revshareglobal.com 2009-12-17

# Best Online Advertising & Revenue Sharing | Global Revenue Sharing

**GRS PRIVACY STATEMENT**

**Completing the Sign-up and Profile**  
GRS will not sell, share, or rent personal information to any 3rd. party. It is necessary that an GRS Affiliate must complete their profile with complete, accurate and verifiable information. GRS does not require your date of birth, social security number, identification number, passport information or drivers license number. The information requested is necessary for effective communication with the GRS Affiliate. 

**Site Security**  
GRS takes every precaution to protect our affiliate’s personal information. Information submitted via our site, is protected to our best efforts and is only accessible to our administration staff. Should the GRS security become breached in any way the GRS Affiliate agrees to hold GRS harmless for any and all damages as a result of any breach. 

**Updating or Correcting Personal Information**  
An GRS Affiliate may correct or update personal information in the restricted affiliate back-office. 

**Communicating With An GRS Affiliate**  
GRS will communicate with the affiliates to provide any information, marketing material, issues relating to accounts, site updates, and service announcements via email. This information may also be posted within the GRS Affiliates Back-office. 

**Notification of Changes in This Privacy Policy**  
Any changes regarding our Privacy Policy will be communicated via email. An GRS Affiliate may notify GRS if they do not agree to GRS’s change or intent to use this information in a manner other than as stated in this statement.
